Adrian Dobrzycki

About me

SOLID-ly oriented on design pattern .NET developer/architect with over 15 years of experience. Big fan of the modular monolith approach and SOA architecture. Open source contributor, frameworks, and libraries creator. Uses SQL to set up new relations. Loving testing and 'it depends' design pattern.

Contact

- adrian.dobrzycki@gmail.com
- born in '86
- · Warsaw, Poland

Core skills

Back-end

- C#, .NET Core2+, 6.0, 5.0, 4.6+, WCF
- CQRS, microservices, modular monolith, IOC, SQL, SOLID, QUEUE-es (RabbitMq, my own sql oriented),
 DDD
- SQL, T-SQL, PostgreSQL, MsSQL, MySQL, Oracle, PL/SQL basics, Dapper, EF Core/6+, MongoDB, LINQ
- Unit/integration testing using: Modulos.Testing, xUnit, NUnit, Mog, NSubstitute and more...
- WebApi, REST, SOAP, JSON/BSON/XML/BINARY, streaming
- JWT, OAuth
- Azure basics

Front-end

- basics: Blazor, React/Native, Typescript, Javascript (ES6+), Angular 4+, jQuery, HTML, CSS
- Winforms, DevExpress

General

- GIT, Docker, YALM, CI/CD
- GitLab, GitHub, Jira, GitLab, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy
- IIS, Kestrel, TCP/IP
- Windows, PowerShell, Windows CE
- SCRUM, R#

Work history

03.2021 - till now - Senior .NET Developer - one of the biggest European e-commerce company

Working on highly loaded products in a supply chain area.

Modular monolith (SOA), .NET Core 3+, .NET 6.0, PostgreSQL, CQRS, DDD, Dapper, RabbitMq, Kafka, GIT, REST, GitLab, Docker, Jira, Rancher, Scrum

06.2018 - 09.2020 - Senior .NET Developer (core team member) - PGE Systemy S.A.

As a member of the core team, I had the possibility to design architecture and core functionalities for the application, developed by dozens of teams and almost a hundred developers.

- taking care of system architecture
- designing core features/approaches (privileges, locking, queues, transactions, testing)
- code refactoring / legacy fighter
- .NET mentoring

Microservices, .NET Core 3+, CQRS, PL/SQL, Oracle, RabbitMq, Angular 8+, GIT, Jira, Jenkins, TypeScript, Scrum

01.2014 - 04.2018 - Architect/Team Leader - PPH POLCAR

Designing architecture and development standards for high performant and scalable applications. Managing team.

- designing system architecture
- managing team, tasks sharing, mentoring

Modular monolith (SOA), NET Core 2.0+, NET 4.6+, CQRS, T-SQL, MySql, EF6, IIS, WinForms + DevExpress, WCF (including SOAP), TCP/IP, GIT, VSTS, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy

01.2012 - 01.2014 - Senior .NET Developer - PPH POLCAR

Maintaining and extending internal systems.

- designing system architecture
- maintaining existing products
- refactoring

T-SQL, WinForms + DevExpress, NET4.0+, NETCF3.5+, Resco, VS2008 + VS2012+, Resharper, TFS, IIS, WCF, WPF, ASPX, IIS, XPO, JavaScript

09.2008 - 01.2012 - .NET Developer - PPH POLCAR

Building WMS and CRM systems for internal company usage. Maintaining existing solutions.

- implementing new features for existing solutions
- maintaining existing products
- designing system architecture for the mobile applications (Windows CE)

T-SQL, WinForms + DevExpress, NET2.0/4.0, NETCF 2.0/3.5, VS2008/2010/2012, Resco, SVN, TFS, IIS, ASMX, ASPX, JavaScript, XPO, Resharper, IIS, Windows CE

Education

• 09.2005 - 09.2009 - Białystok University of Technology (Bachelor of Engineering)

Languages

- English (B2)
- Polish (native)

Hobbies

Programming, good book/movie, bicycle, chess. Participation in meetups and technical conferences.

More at

- github: https://github.com/adobrzyc
- linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adrian-dobrzycki-a26833134
- stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/5320247/adobrzyc

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed by anyone for the purpose of current and future recruitment processes under the Personal Data Protection Act. I provide my personal data voluntarily understanding that without it a proper recruitment process is deemed impossible.